HARIKA BULLA

SENIOR FACETS/SQL LEAD AND MANAGER

CONTACT INFORMATION

- +91 966 337 3034
- hari.ch.gd@gmail.com
- Bangalore

SUMMARY

Award winning Senior designer in FACETS with 12.8 years of experience possessing ability to build custom solutions using ORACLE/Microsoft SQL server. Proficient in analyzing proposals (RFP's) towards gaining new line of business. Strong team management with higher customer credence.

SKILLS

- Domain Knowledge (US Health Care)
 - FACETS Claims, Encounters, Membership, Providers, Product, Billing, Capitation
 - EDI, HIPAA Gateway
 - Health Care Interoperability
 - Facets Integration with JIVA (ZeOmega Care Management)
- Technical Expertise
 - Oracle/Sybase/Microsoft SQL Server PL/SQL, VB Scripting, Oracle APEX, Pervasive Data Integrator
- Project Management and Software development
- Proficient experience in traditional Waterfall/Agile model

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University, Anantapur

POST GRADUATE (M.TECH) IN CONTROL SYSTEMS, CLASS OF 2009

GNITS Hyderabad

GRADUATE (B.TECH) IN ELECTRONICS AND COMMUNICATIONS, CLASS OF 2006

Chinmaya Junior College - Class XII

Kendriya Vidyalaya -Class X (C.B.S.E Board)

AWARDS RECEIVED

- Customer Focus Award Sep 2019
- Associate of the Quarter Q4 2018
- Associate of the month -2017, 2016

SKILLS [Continued...]

- Budgeting and Cost Analysis
- Resource planning
- Staff and User Training
- Process Improvement

COLLABORATED CLIENTS

• *Wellpoint*: April 2010 - April 2011

• AmeriHealth: July 2011- November 2011

• Blue Shield: Dec 2011-Feb 2016 of California

• *Presbyterian:* March 2016 - June 2021 *Health Plan*

• Caresource: March 2022 - Till Date

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Lead Consultant

INFOSYS - BANGALORE

NOVEMBER 2022 - TILL DATE - FTE MARCH 2022 - OCTOBER 2022 - SUBCON (RADIANT SYSTEMS INC.)

Developer/Designer

- Analyze user stories, Interact and work with Client on agile model
- Design and develop SQL scripts, Stored Procedures using SQL server
- Develop test cases for enhancement and perform extensive Unit and Assembly Testing
- Understand Defects/Incidents that are raised when an application error occurs in the system in any of Production/Non Production Environments and to resolve issue
- Create or modify jobs in BOT/Tidal scheduler

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY [Continued...]

Senior Product Specialist

COGNIZANT TECHNOLOGY SOLUTIONS - BANGALORE

DECEMBER 2009 TO JUNE 2021

Developer/Designer

- Develop programs such as Stored Procedures/Functions/Packages to update/extract data in/from Facets per Business Requirements
- Create end to end automation solutions for clients involving feasibility study, design, architecture, development, testing and deployment of Facets Interfaces
- Performance improvement
- Build batch subsystem (schedule and orchestration) to execute core Facets batches and any custom Facets-related batches (Extracts, Interfaces, Recurring Reports)

Lead

- Lead a team of 10 designers
- Monitor regular tasks and perform code reviews
- Analyze and Provide estimates for new **Project Proposals** (RFP's) around Facets
- Train and mentor new entrees
- Validate and share Project Invoices to Client on monthly basis for Remittance receivables
- Perform Technical Audits with respect to external Teams
- Represent team and demonstrate Work items administered in Project as part of Technical Audit
- Validate technical strengths of new resources to check their fitment in Project